Guide to the Department of Zoology records, 1873-1965.
Department of Zoology records
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Correspondence with LaMont C. Cole 1964-1965
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Personnel Director, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Peterson, Arthur H., 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Placement Service, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Prudential Group Life Insurance, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Research, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Schane, Harry P., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Swart, E. A., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Summer Session, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Traffic Control, Board of, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Wang, Chia-sheng Johnson, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 108)
- Series III. Applications for Instructorship
  - Alden, Roland H., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Altland, Paul D., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Baker, Burton L., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Bernstein, Joseph G., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Bishop, David W., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Browman, Ludvig G., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Buyse, Adrian, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Eversole, W. J., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Gayer, Kenneth H., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Groat, Richard A., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Grunwald, Peter, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Hard, W. L., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Horn, Edward C., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Karolyi, E. Joesph, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Mahoney, John J., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - MacFarland, William E., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Murray, Raymond G., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Noback, Charles R., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Piatt, Jean Barnett, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Rahn, Hermann, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Tucker, Gordon H., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Williams, William Lane, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    Includes several articles written or co-written by Williams
- Series IV. Administrative Records
  - Myers, W. I. - Dean, 1944-1948 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Promotions, Agr., 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Ratings for Employees, 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Salary Scale, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Budget - Agriculture, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 145)
- Series V. Personnel Records
  - Former Department Personnel, 1935-1945 (Box 9, Folder 146)
  - Aber, Marianne R., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Adelman, Howard B., 1949-1966 (Box 9, Folder 148)
  - Allen, Arthur A., 1906-1948 (Box 9, Folder 149)
  - Allen, Elsa G., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - Alvarez, Louis, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 151)
  - Ambrose, Harrison W., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 152)
  - Anderson, John W., 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 153)
  - Angevine, Jay B., 1949-1955 (Box 9, Folder 154)
  - Axtell, Harold H., 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 155)
  - Barden, Robert B., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - Belman, Anita L., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Bensadown (DiSanto), Paula E., 1956-1960 (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Benton, Allen H., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - Bequaert, Helen, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - Bergeron, John A., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - Berkenfield, J. Alan, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Berry, Spencer J., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Bihari, Bernard, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Bishop, Jane E., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Bivins, Phyllis, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Blaustein, Mordecai P., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Bloedel, Prentice, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Bodemer, Charles W., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Boggs, Barbara J., 1957 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Bond, Charles F., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Borgmann, Dorothea L., 1957 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Bowman, Roger H., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Briggs, Richard G., 1959 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Brightenback, George E., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - Brockway, Alan P., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - Brockway (Fink), Barbara A., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Brooks, Barbara, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Brumsted, Harlan B., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Burnett, Allison L., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Cameron, Austin W., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Caswell, Herbert H., Jr., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Cattell, Eleth, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Cavender, Finis L., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Chiquoine, A. Duncan, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Cohen, Nathan, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Collias, Elsie C., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Cook, Ellen T., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Crocker, Denton W., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Dahlen, Mary Ellen, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Davis, Robert P., 1957 (Box 9, Folder 191)
  - Davis, Ronald B., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Day, Holliday T., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 193)
  - Deubler, Earl E., Jr., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - Diamond, Marian C., 1957 (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - Doremus, Henry M., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 196)
  - Douglas, Steven D., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Dunham, Anna L., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 198)
  - Eadie, W. Robert, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Edinger, Barbara E., 1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Evans, Howard E., 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Felice, Alfred J., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Ferguson, John C., 1958-1962 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Fisher, Robert L., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Foster, Neal R., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Gerold, Nicolas, 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ghiradella, Helen T., 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gibbs, Robert H., Jr., 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Gilbert, Lawrence I., 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Gilio, Joseph L., 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gimbrone, Michael A., 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Gladfelter, William B., 1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Glasser, Lewis, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Goode, Robert P., 1957 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gottschang, Jack L., 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gould, Edwin, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Green, Roger H., 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Griffin, Donald R., 1947-1953 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Includes note-cards listing all of Griffin's publications
  - Gustafson, John A., 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hall, Marjorie E., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Hamilton, William J., Jr., 1926-1949 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Hammel, Harold T., 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hart, Dorothy K., 1957 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Haynes, Julian F., 1960 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Heath, Gordon W., 1950-1956 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hertz, Philip, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Hess, Betsey W., 1959 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Hillman, Herbert R., Jr., 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Hock, Raymond J., 1948 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Hough, Barbara R., 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Huls, Harriett N., 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Hu--bert (Stern), Albreta M., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Hyde, John L., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Jameson, Evertett W., Jr., 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Johnson, Frederic H., 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Johnson, Harry McClure, 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Jones, Helen E., 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Jordan, Robert M., 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Kallen, Frank C., 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Kamrin, Robert P., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Kare, Morley R., 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Kellers, Isabel N., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Kellogg, P. Paul, 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Kelton, Audrey W., 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Kent, John F., 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Kessel, Brina, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Kezer, Leonard J., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Knobil, Ernest R., 1948 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Kostyo, Jack L., 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - LaMarca, Michael J., 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Laufer, Hans, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Lauff, George H., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Levy, Alan M., 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Linder, Harris J., 1952-1956 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Livezey, Robert, 1944-1946 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Loeb, Marcia J., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Ludlam, Stuart D., 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Lux, Mary S., 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Lyman, Charles P., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - MacNoab, Ann, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Maguire, Bassett, Jr., 1952-1955 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Marvin, Lorraine, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - McClure, Robert C., 1959 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - McManus, Lawrence R., 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Mekeel, Amy G., 1918-1945 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Merriam, G. Aileen, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Merriam, H. Gray, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Meyerowitz, Carol O., 196- (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Midgett, Mary E., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Miller, Helen C., 1960 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Mirarchi, Donna R., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Montagna, William, 1941-1944 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Moore, Maxine R., 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Moorhead, Lynn, 195- (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Moss, Sanford A., 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Mouser, Gilbert W., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Neporent, Lewis M., 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Newcomer, W. Stanley, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Niemer, William T., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Northrop, Theodore G., 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Nutting, William B., 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Oren, Mark E., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Papez, James W., 1930-1950 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Parkes, Kenneth C., 1947-1949 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Parks, Harold F., 1945-1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Paul, Dorothy A., 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Perlman, Preston L., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Pernaa, Judith E., 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Pliske, Thomas E., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Poritsky, Raphael L., 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Porter, Randall C., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Potash, Milton, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Raney, Edward C., 1936-1949 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Raney, M. Gail, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Rawson, Kenneth S., 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reeves, R. Blake, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Includes several publications by Reeves
  - Remillard, Guy L., 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Renk, Mary A., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Rinard, Harold G., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Rinell, Kermit T., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Robins, C. Richard, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Alan S., 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Roecker, Robert M., 1948 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ross, Robert D., 1946-1948 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Russell, Glenn V., 1947-1950 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Salpeter, Miriam M., 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Satterfield, James D., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Sauer, Leonard A., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Saunders, Harry L., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Schane, Harry P., 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Schechter, Alan N., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Scheuing, Marilyn R., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Schlernitzauer, Donald, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Schmidt, Janet E., 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Schneiderman, Howard A., 1953-1960 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Seaman, Arlene R., 1944-1949 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Senyard, Juanita, 1944-1947 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Shapiro, Bettison E., 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Shaw (Tryon), Gayle R., 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Shelar, Eugene, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Sheldon, Andrew L., 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Shimp, Norman H., 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Short, Lester L., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Sidman, Richard L., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Singer, Marcus, 1951-1960 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Singer, Marcus, 1956-1961 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    Letters addressing the suspension of Dr. Singer
  - Sisk, Mary O., 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Smead, Martha E., 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Snyder, Richard C., 1942-1963 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Sorokin, Sergei P., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Spencer, Mazzare, 1944-1950 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Stelling, Valerie C., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Stephens, Robert J., 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Stiven, Alan E., 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Strauss, Fritz, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Suttkus, Royal D., 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Sutton, George M., 1932-1946 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Taylor, Clark A., 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Taylor, Joan N., 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Taylor, Peter B., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Togut, Allen J., 1956 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Troyer, John R., 1949-1952 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Valiela, Ivan, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Van der Kloot, William G., 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Van Vleck, David B., 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Veit, Diana J., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Voneida, Theodore J., 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Walcott, Charles G., 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Walsh, Raymond R., 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Wanlass, Stanley A., Jr., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Ward, Margaret C., 1942-1946 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Warner, Dwain W., 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Warner, Eldon D., 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Webster, Douglas B., 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Werdegar, David, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - White, Joan F., 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Whitehurst, Jesse D., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Wickersham, A. A. Tilney, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Windnagle, M. Shirley, 1949-1953 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Winter, Peter M., 1957 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Witschi, Thomas H., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Wolfrum, William H., 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Wolin, Lee R., 195- (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Wolk, Robert G., 195- (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Wortman, Louise C., 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Wright, Albert H., 1908-1947 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Young, Benjamin P., 1919-1952 (Box 11, Folder 85)
- Series VI. Photographs
  - Two envelopes containing photos of lampreys (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Six envelopes containing photos of lampreys (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Three envelopes containing photos of toads, one envelope containing photos of lab equipment (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Large envelope containing photos of lampreys (Box 12)
- Series VII. Zoology Department Records
  - New York State Veterinary College Library inventory book of Periodicals in the Zoology Library, September 1958 (Box 12)
  - Inventory book of equipment, slides, etc. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Book detailing the space requirements in the proposed new animal biology building (Box 12)
  - Record of zoological specimens, one volume, 1882-1897 (Box 13)
    Ledger book of acquired specimens, including brains.
  - Miscellaneous papers, including correspondence, reports, memorandums, 1960 Annual Report to the Dean, Five Year Progress Report on Physiology and Biochemistry of Insect Growth and Differentiation 1954-1959, and a list of publications by Schneiderman, 1960-1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Candidates for position of Invertebrate Zoologist: Haskin, Hutchins, Edmondson (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence concerning appointment of Harold F. Parks as a Professor in the Department of Zoology, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence concerning new position in Physical Anthropology and Human Development, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Includes Growth and Development of the Chimpanzee; a Longitudinal and Comparative Study, Birth Order and Birth Weight in the Chimpanzee, and "Growth of Guamanian Children"-Some Methodological Questions by James A. Gavan
  - Replies to letters regarding new position in Physical Anthropology and Human Development, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence concerning Dr. Griffin's replacement, 1952-1960 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Includes Nucleoprotein Complexes of Sperm Nuclei by Jay Barton II.
  - New Building Requirements, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Includes photograph of Stimson Hall
    Includes pamphlet on Harvard Biological Laboratories
    Includes pamphelt on the New Zoological Laboratory of the University of Pennsylvania
  - Temporary Appointment in Embryology, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Rejected Applications for the General and Cellular Physiology position, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Includes several publications by Ray M. Iverson
  - Anderson, John M., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Vallentyne, John R., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Buck, John B., 1945 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Crescitelli, Frederick, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Erikson, G. E., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Galambos, Robert, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Grenell, Robert Gordon, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Sawyer, Wilbur H., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Griffin, Donald R., 1945 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kraus, Bertram S., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Metz, Charles B., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Preer, John R., Jr., 1951 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Renshaw, Birdsey, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Prescott, David M., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence with senior prospects for Physiology position, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Menaker, Michael, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Sprague, James Mather, 19-- (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Straus, William L., Jr., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Hodgson, Edward S., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Applications for general Zoology position, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    Includes publications by Morris Rockstein, Cadet Hammond Hand, Jr., and Bronislaw Honigberg
  - Applications for Zoology position, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Tappen, Neil C., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Gross, Paul Randolph, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Applications for Physiology position, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Morrison, Peter R., 1960 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Josephson, Robert K., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Willis, John S., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Louderback, Allan, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - South, Frank E., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Fiore, Carl, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Toft, Robert Jens, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Carlson, Albert, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Allen, Kenneth, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Wright, David Loren and Holmes, W. N., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Poulson, Thomas L., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Hill, Robert B., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Eckert, Roger O., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Not interested responses for Embryology position, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Suggested candidates for Embryology position, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Rhea, Robert P., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Smith, Arlan E. S., 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    Includes publication by Arlan E. S. Smith
  - Cairns, John M., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Klingener, David, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Stanley, Hugh P., 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Small, James, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Runner, Meredith N., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Shephard, David, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Kahn, Arnold, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - McConkey, Edwin H., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - G, correspondents by last name, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Graduate Students, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Sabine, G. H., 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Sage Research Fund, 1940-1942 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Meigs, R. B., 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Draft Status of Zoology Staff, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Responses to candidate suggestions, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - List of Department publications, various newspaper articles about Department staff, information on retired staff, information on Cornell Endowment Funds, miscellaneous correspondence, 1933-1958 (Box 14, Folder 66)